https://www.legere.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Welcome to www.legere.com. Please read the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy carefully before ordering any products from us (the “Products”) or accessing our website (the “Website”). The terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy will be updated from time to time and all revisions will be posted on the Website.  We strongly recommend that you review this Privacy Policy regularly, to ensure you are aware of these changes.
1.      INTRODUCTION
As a part of the sale of the Products and the operation of the Website, Légère Reeds collects personal information.  Légère Reeds respects the privacy of its customers and believes that such information deserves protection. This Privacy Policy will explain what types of personal information Légère Reeds collects, what uses are made of such information, and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.
At all times, it is your decision as to whether you wish to purchase the Products or access the Website and provide us with information about yourself.  At no time will we collect, use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than those listed in this Privacy Policy without your consent.
Throughout this policy we refer to “Légère Reeds”, which means Légère Reeds Ltd., the seller of the Products and the owner of the Website, and its affiliates.
2.      COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
In order to effectively deliver the Products and associated services to its customers, Légère Reeds must collect certain personal information. Such information would include, for example, the customer’s name, address, phone number, fax number and email address. Légère Reeds must also collect certain financial information (such as credit card information) in order to process payments for the Products.
You may visit and browse the Website without registering and without directly providing any personal information. In other instances, such as when sending Légère Reeds an email message, requesting further information concerning the Products, or providing us with feedback, we may require that you provide personal information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, phone number, and fax number.
Where you provide personal information directly to another organization at another website through a link on our Website, Légère Reeds shall not be responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of such information, and we encourage you to examine the other organization’s privacy policy.
3.      USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Légère Reeds may use personal information provided by you in the following ways:
To deliver the Products including:
processing payments;
shipping products;
general administration.
To process technical and customer service-related inquiries. To personalize the delivery of content and information to you.
Légère Reeds may also use personal information and data collected to generate aggregate statistics and reports for internal use. However, these statistics and reports will not contain any information that would identify individual users of the Products such as you.
4.      DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
As a normal part of providing the Products, Légère Reeds must disclose certain personal information to third party service providers. For example, Légère Reeds must provide your address to our delivery service. Légère Reeds must also provide certain financial information to credit card processing companies in order to process payments for the Products.
Your non-aggregated specific personal information will not be sold, rented or made available to anyone other than Légère Reeds unless you have given us express permission to do so.
Légère Reeds reserves the right at any time to disclose any personal information: (i) to comply with any applicable law or regulation; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to the sale of the Products or operation of the Website; and/or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Légère Reeds and its users, partners, providers, licensors and/or merchants.
5.      REVISIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY
If Légère Reeds decides to change this Privacy Policy, changes will be posted on the Website, so that you will always be aware of what personal information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
6.    ERROR CORRECTION
You have the option of correcting factual errors in your individually identifiable information on our computer systems.  To protect your privacy and security, you will be required to provide appropriate identification before this information is altered. To correct your information, simply send a written request via Contact-Us
7.    CONSENT
By purchasing a Product, sending a request for information, or using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Légère Reeds, as described by this Privacy Policy.  If at any time you wish to withdraw your consent, simply send a written request via Contact-Us.
8.    QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS
Légère Reeds welcomes your feedback regarding this Privacy Policy. Please direct any comments, suggestions or concerns to our privacy officer via contact-us
PRODUCTS
STRENGTH CHARTS
SOUND CHALLENGE
BETA TESTING
FAQ
ONLINE STORE
CONTACT US
EXCHANGE OF STRENGTH
Copyright © 2020 Légère Reeds LTD.
Retailers
© Copyright © 2020 Légère Reeds LTD.
Never miss a beat
Get the latest Légère news HERE!
Email*
First Name*
X
